What do you think?
どうですか?
Have you had a boyfriend since then?
あれから、彼氏はできました?
I haven't been able to do it.
できてないです
Haven't you done it?
できてない?
No.
ないです
So what is the word eh?
じゃあ、えっという言葉は?
I haven't.
してないです
Haven't you?
してないですか?
No.
ないです
How about alone?
一人ではどうですか?
Yes, there is.
ありますね
Alone after all?
一人でやっぱり?
Yes, there is.
ありますね
Do you use toys?
おもちゃ使ったり?
yes.
はい
I see, I see.
なるほど、なるほど
Has anything increased since then?
あれから、何か増えたりしました?
Like the number of women.
女の人の数とか
It increased a little.
ちょいちょい増えた
After all, it has increased.
やっぱり増えちゃった
yes.
はい
After all, it feels like using toys.
やっぱりおもちゃ使ったりして、って感じですかね
Well then, right away,
そしたらですね、早速なんですけど、
Shall I take off my clothes for a moment?
ちょっと服脱いちゃいましょうか
yes.
はい
Is it okay if I cut you off a little?
ちょっと手抜けてもらってもいいですか?
Well then, let's open our legs.
じゃあ、足開いちゃいましょうか
Shall I take off my underwear?
下着も脱いちゃいましょうか
Well, sorry.
まあ、ごめんなさい
Then, can I have you stand for a moment?
そしたら、ちょっと立ってもらっていいですか?
Then, would you like me to open it again?
そしたら、そのままもう一回、あそこ開いてもらいますか
Shall I take a shower first?
シャワー、最初は浴びちゃおうか
yes.
はい
However, I would like you to clean mine up a bit.
ただ、俺のもちょっと綺麗にしてもらおうかな
Yeah.
うん
Are you okay over there?
あそこ大丈夫ですか?
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
Then I guess they'll do it orally.
そしたら、口でやるらしいかな
Yeah, sorry.
うん、ごめんなさい
Then I'll go to sleep.
そしたら、寝ていこうか
Go here too.
こっちも行って
Let's hug your legs.
足抱え込んじゃおう
Then just go.
そしたら、そのままで行ってね
Open your legs.
足開いて
yes.
はい
I'm going to sleep.
寝ちゃうよ
yes.
はい
Let's turn this way for a moment.
ちょっと、こっち向きにしようか
So, show me well.
で、よく見せて
Try to hold on.
踏ん張ってみて
It's cheaper to be on your knees.
膝立ちになった方が安いよ
Yeah.
うん
It's okay, thank you.
大丈夫、ありがとう
Show me well.
よく見せて
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう